

#### CONTACT

Mobile: +49 177 477 8501 E-mail: giorgio.torre8@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Tenhil GmbH & Co KG

Software Developer January 2023 - current

## stellenanzeigen.de

Junior Software Developer June 2021 - December 2022

# **Bombardier Transportation UK**

Project Commercial Manager September 2016 - May 2021

#### **EDUCATION**

# Cranfield University (UK)

MSc in Manufacturing Systems September 2014 - August 2015

# Pisa University (IT)

BSc & MSc in Industrial Engineering September 2010 - August 2014

### LANGUAGE SKILLS

# English / Italian Native / Bilingual proficiency

#### German

Professional working proficiency

# GIORGIO TORRE

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

#### **PROFILE**

I'm a self-taught software developer with a passion for challenges, problem-solving, and delivering projects. I'm a self-starter dedicated to acquiring new skills and honing existing ones. My experiences have forged a strong mix of technical know-how and project delivery acumen, a must in today's fast-paced work world.

#### **SKILLS**

- TypeScript / JavaScript
- React / Next.js / Remix.run / Node.js
- HTML5 / CSS3 / Tailwind / Styled Components / SASS
- Redux / Redux Toolkit / RTK Query
- Jest / React Testing Library

## **PROJECTS**

#### Our Wedding

Stack: Remix / Tailwind / Typescript / Vercel

Fully responsive wedding site to manage RSVP and info sharing with guests - <a href="https://www.giorgio-laura.com/">https://www.giorgio-laura.com/</a> (pwd: Hir3Me!:D)

#### Personal Portfolio

Stack: Remix / Tailwind / Typescript / Vercel

Fully responsive portfolio app showcasing my work - <a href="https://giorgio-portfolio-towerbrother.vercel.app/">https://giorgio-portfolio-towerbrother.vercel.app/</a>

#### Weather App

Stack: React / SASS

SPA weather forecast - data from OpenWeatherAPI - https://towerbrother.github.io/weather-app

### JavaScript Calculator

Stack: HTML / CSS / Javascript

Simple, modern-looking calculator coded with Vanilla JS - <a href="https://towerbrother.github.io/JS-calculator">https://towerbrother.github.io/JS-calculator</a>

#### LINKS

https://github.com/towerbrother/
https://www.linkedin.com/in/giorgiotorre/